Story Five - Jon Has Lots of Homework
Jon is in high school.
He has lots of homework.
Clare is a university student.
She has lots of homework, too.
Jon does not like homework.
He likes to play on his computer.
Clare likes reading and writing.
She does her homework every day.
Clare is Jon's older sister.
She always makes him do his homework.
Here is the same story told in a different way.
I am in high school.
I have lots of homework.
Clare is a university student.
She has lots of homework, too.
I do not like homework.
I like to play on my computer.
Clare likes reading and writing.
She does her homework every day.
Clare is my older sister.
She always makes me do my homework.
One: Jon is a high school student.
Is Jon a high school student?
Yes, Jon is a high school student.
Two: Jon has a lot of homework.
Does Jon have a lot of homework?
Yes, Jon has a lot of homework.
Three: Clare is a university student.
Is Clare a high school student?
No, Clare is not a high school student.
She is a university student.
Four: Jon likes playing on his computer.
Does Jon like playing on his computer?
Yes, Jon likes playing on his computer.
Five: Clare likes reading and writing.
Does Clare like watching movies?
No, Clare likes reading and writing.
Six: Clare does her homework every day.
Does Clare do her homework every day?
Yes, Clare does her homework every day.
Seven: Clare is Jon's older sister.
Are Jon and Clare related?
Yes, Jon and Clare are related.
Clare is Jon's older sister.
Eight: Clare makes Jon do his homework every day.
Does Clare make Jon do his homework?
Yes, Clare makes Jon do his homework every day.